They have actually claimed at highlights that I am the biggest consumer
of glitter spray.
I think that is a merit.
Tjena Kenneth!
Hello Hello!
How's it going?
It's good, it's full roll.
Much that is happening now.
Yes it is.
Where are we somewhere?
Now we are at Söder, at Medborgarplatsen, at Björn's garden,
at a store called highlights.
What are you talking about?
But to paint it you need some color.
Yes, that is why we are at this deal now.
What was its name?
Highlights.
And then we will go in there and then we will see if we can find any color.
Yes.
Now I'm out in deep water.
Yes now you are out in deep water.
I have no idea.
What to do in here?
Here there are lots of different colors, different types
And everything from airbrush to pens to spray cans.
Clothes are even available.
They have everything here.
Maybe some different versions.
I can agree with that.
But here it is Montana Gold that applies.
But how long do these colors last?
We have had cars that have lasted for several years and are
So that the color starts to flake in some way.
But then it is just putting on again.
After all, it's not more difficult than that.
I'm not looking to get a car that should be super shiny as well.
If one does not now put on a lot of clear lacquer
That's another thing.
Now things are starting to happen.
Yes okay, then.
I get some stuff that you have thought of.
So we can tell loud is that if you are going to choose silver
so you choose a matte silver and not chrome
Because it is overpowerable.
Yes I know.
It is nice to work in the same shade.
Yes several shifts to make
Shadows and stuff.
So I thought about some caps too.
Yes, absolutely, that.
You have to have, otherwise no one will be good.
It is great with those with the usual caps, but they are not good for everything.
Talking to nozzles?
Yes nozzles, ie caps.
There it was all kinds of different.
A jungle.
I have started to learn this.
Are you kidding me?
I thought there was a nozzle.
It doesn't.
If you are wrong then it will be wrong I can promise.
Many, many, many different colors.
As many colors as I have pens.
The tank lid?
Yes, it became a special you can say.
There was a rocket that goes into the fuel cap and then I had on melt glue
And so I did as it almost looked organic.
And then I paint over that and then I paint that little grenade
And so there so it looks like a grenade in the fuel lid.
My feeling for this with gasoline prices and stuff.
Hello Hello!
How's it going?
Yes it is good
Welcome to Lidköping, the city where it always blows headwinds.
Both I and Kenneth you think have a very fun car.
What do you think Kenneth?
Yes, here it is windy.
Are there three walls and it blows straight in here
So there will be color everywhere.
Now we will start where we will start with a little dark green.
Put on the skis and then we'll go over to another shade
And further and further.
Damn, now I'm so excited to start.